https://pintangle.com/privacy-policy/

Skip to content
Home Privacy Policy
What personal data is collected on this site and why
Comments
When visitors leave comments on the site I collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.
An anonymised string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After your comment is approved, your profile picture is visible to the public next to your comment.
Embedded content from other websites
Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.
These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracking your interaction with the embedded content.
While visiting our store, we collect:
Products you’ve viewed: we’ll use this to, for example, show you products you’ve recently viewed
Location, IP address and browser type: we’ll use this for purposes like estimating taxes and shipping
We’ll also use cookies to keep track of cart contents while you’re browsing our site.
When you purchase from us, we’ll ask you to provide information including your name, billing address, shipping address, email address, phone number, credit card/payment details and optional account information like username and password. We’ll use this information for purposes, such as, to:
Send you information about your account and order
Respond to your requests, including refunds and complaints
Process payments and prevent fraud
Comply with any legal obligations we have, such as calculating taxes
Improve our store offerings
Analytics
Who I share your data with
Other than as listed above I do not share your data. I do not on-sell your data to third parties.
How long your data is retained
If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely.
What rights you have over your data
If you have left comments on this site, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data held about you, including any data you have provided. You can also request that any personal data I hold about you is erased. This does not include any data I am obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.
Where I send your data
Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.
Contact information
You can contact me via the contact page.
About
Pintangle's focus is on hand embroidery and crazy quilting. Here you will find tutorials, free patterns, stitch instructions, and tips and stitchers eye candy!
Subscribe to Pintangle
Enter your email to subscribe to Pintangle and have it delivered to your inbox when I update.
Email Address
Subscribe
New Book!
My book Creative Stitches for Contemporary Embroidery: Visual Guide to 120 Essential Stitches for Stunning Designs
is out now!My Crazy Quilting Book!
My book The Visual Guide to Crazy Quilting Design: Simple Stitches, Stunning Results is out now.Stitchers Templates
I designed these templates with stitchers in mind. With them you can create hundreds of different patterns to embroider.
Available Here
Social Places
Recent Commentssharonb on Creative Stitches for Contemporary Embroiderysharonb on Creative Stitches for Contemporary EmbroideryCLAIRE AVOINETTE on Creative Stitches for Contemporary EmbroideryPauline Holbrook on Creative Stitches for Contemporary Embroiderysharonb on Creative Stitches for Contemporary EmbroideryCategoriesCategories
Select Category
100 details for 100 days
2020 Crazy quilt
Art and Design
Art and Studio journals
Beading and Buttons
Book and Paper arts
Books
Privacy & Cookies: This site uses cookies. By continuing to use this website, you agree to their use.
To find out more, including how to control cookies, see here:
100 details for 100 days (100)
2020 Crazy quilt (25)
Art and Design (205)
Art and Studio journals (120)
Beading and Buttons (49)
Book and Paper arts (82)
Books (74)
Challenges (168)
Crazy quilt details (601)
Crazy Quilt Journal Project (20)
Crazy quilting (294)
Creative Embroidery (5)
Diamond block crazy quilt (48)
Fabric Books (1)
Fiber and Textile Arts (605)
Free patterns (136)
Hand Embroidery (258)
Hand embroidery stitches (171)
Have a Cuppa (301)
Hussif Mini Challenge (14)
Lace quilt (65)
Long Band Sampler (619)
Resources (205)
Samplers (49)
Sharon B's CQ Templates (7)
Stitch Dictionary (76)
Stitch Explorer 2009 (14)
Take a Stitch Tuesday (65)
Take it Further challenge (17)
Web (81)
Work in Progress (224)
International shipping $10 flat rate, free for orders over $100.00
0%
